export const chapter = "Chapter - 8: Adjectives: Degrees of Comparison";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "What does the Positive Degree of an adjective do?",
          optionA: "Compares qualities",
          optionB: "Describes a quality in simple terms",
          optionC: "Indicates the maximum quality",
          correctAnswer: "Describes a quality in simple terms",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In Comparative Degree, what word is used to compare the quality of a person or thing?",
          optionA: "More",
          optionB: "Than",
          optionC: "The",
          correctAnswer: "Than",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is added to form the Comparative Degree of most Positive Degrees?",
          optionA: "er",
          optionB: "est",
          optionC: "ly",
          correctAnswer: "er",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When the Positive Degree ends in 'e,' what is added to form the Superlative Degree?",
          optionA: "er",
          optionB: "est",
          optionC: "ly",
          correctAnswer: "est",
        },
        {
          question:
            "If the Positive Degree ends in 'y' preceded by a consonant, what is changed to form the Comparative Degree?",
          optionA: "y to e",
          optionB: "y to i",
          optionC: "y to a",
          correctAnswer: "y to i",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which adjective has a set pattern for changing it from Positive Degree to Comparative and Superlative Degrees?",
          optionA: "Good",
          optionB: "Interesting",
          optionC: "Old",
          correctAnswer: "Good",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What word is used to compare two qualities in the Comparative Degree?",
          optionA: "And",
          optionB: "With",
          optionC: "Than",
          correctAnswer: "Than",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'Manas is the youngest in the class,' which Degree of Comparison is used?",
          optionA: "Positive",
          optionB: "Comparative",
          optionC: "Superlative",
          correctAnswer: "Superlative",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How is the Comparative Degree of the adjective 'busy' formed?",
          optionA: "busier",
          optionB: "more busy",
          optionC: "busiest",
          correctAnswer: "busier",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which adjective follows a different pattern in forming its Comparative and Superlative Degrees?",
          optionA: "Beautiful",
          optionB: "Old",
          optionC: "Interesting",
          correctAnswer: "Old",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "Positive Degree tells a quality in ______ terms.",
          optionA: "complex",
          optionB: "simple",
          optionC: "comparative",
          correctAnswer: "simple",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Comparative Degree compares the quality of a person or thing ______ another.",
          optionA: "with",
          optionB: "by",
          optionC: "than",
          correctAnswer: "than",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Superlative Degree tells that the quality has the ______ of that quality.",
          optionA: "minimum",
          optionB: "maximum",
          optionC: "average",
          correctAnswer: "maximum",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Comparative Degree of most Positive Degrees is formed by adding ______.",
          optionA: "est",
          optionB: "ly",
          optionC: "er",
          correctAnswer: "er",
        },
        {
          question:
            "If the Positive Degree ends in 'e,' the Superlative Degree is formed by adding ______.",
          optionA: "er",
          optionB: "ly",
          optionC: "est",
          correctAnswer: "est",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Comparative Degree of an adjective ending in 'y' preceded by a consonant is formed by changing 'y' to ______.",
          optionA: "a",
          optionB: "i",
          optionC: "e",
          correctAnswer: "i",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Some adjectives have no set pattern for changing them from Positive Degree to Comparative and Superlative Degrees, such as ______.",
          optionA: "good",
          optionB: "interesting",
          optionC: "old",
          correctAnswer: "good",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The 'Green Flag' button in Scratch activates a script when the ______ button is clicked.",
          optionA: "stop",
          optionB: "go",
          optionC: "pause",
          correctAnswer: "go",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In Scratch, to make a sprite move backward, add a ______ number of steps to the 'move' block.",
          optionA: "positive",
          optionB: "negative",
          optionC: "zero",
          correctAnswer: "negative",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which adjective follows a different pattern in forming its Comparative and Superlative Degrees?",
          optionA: "Beautiful",
          optionB: "Old",
          optionC: "Interesting",
          correctAnswer: "Old",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "Positive Degree tells a quality in simple terms.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Comparative Degree compares the quality of a person or thing with others.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Superlative Degree indicates the minimum of a quality.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Comparative Degree is formed by adding 'ly' to most Positive Degrees.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Superlative Degree of an adjective ending in 'e' is formed by adding 'est'.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Comparative Degree of an adjective ending in 'y' preceded by a consonant is formed by changing 'y' to 'i'.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Some adjectives have a set pattern for changing them from Positive Degree to Comparative and Superlative Degrees.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The 'Green Flag' button in Scratch pauses the script for a given time.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In Scratch, to make a sprite move backward, add a positive number of steps to the 'move' block.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Control Blocks in Scratch are used to stop all added sound on all sprites.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
